Now that you've had a little introduction to the theory behind k-fold
你已经对 K 折交叉验证背后的理论
cross validation,
有所了解
it might not surprise you to know that we're going to take a look at the code.
今天我们学习代码 这对你来说应该不困难
K-fold cross validation is supported in the cross validation
K 折交叉验证可在 sklearn 中的
set of functions that are available in sklearn.
交叉验证函数集中使用
So I want to show you what it looks like when it's being deployed.
接下来 我将向你展示该功能部署后的样子
The code that I have right here is code that you're actually
这里的代码对你来说
already familiar with.
应该不陌生
This is the code that we used in the very first mini project,
这些代码是我们在第一个微型项目中使用过的
to identify the author of the emails.
用来确认写电子邮件的人
Was it Sara, or is it Chris?
是 Sara 还是 Chris
I'm just using a Gaussian Naive Bayes.
我使用的是高斯朴素贝叶斯
I'm keeping track of the training time, the predicting time and
我记录了此分类器的
the accuracy that I get for this classifier.
训练时间、预测时间以及准确性
Remember, the features that I am using are the words in the emails and
注意我使用的特征是电子邮件中的字词
I'm trying to predict who wrote the email based on the vocabulary that's
而我要达到的目的是 根据电子邮件中使用的词汇推测
being used.
写电子邮件的人
Up above that I see some feature transforms that I'm doing,
这上方是我进行的一些特征转换
I am reading in the text, and I'm doing some feature selection.
我首先读取文字的内容 然后进行特征选择
These are all things that we've talked about,
以上是我们之前讲过的内容
so I won't belabor them too much right now.
这里就不详述了
More interesting bit of code is up here.
这段代码更有意思
The first thing that I do is from sklearn.cross_validation I import KFold,
首先我从 sklearn.cross_validation 中导入 KFold
which is the name of their k-fold cross-validation function.
这是 sklearn 中 K 折交叉验证函数的名称
Then I have to declare a k-fold object, which accepts two arguments.
然后我必须声明一个 K 折对象 该对象接受两个参数
One is the number of items in the total data set.
一个是数据总集中的项目数量
So in this case,
在这个例子中
I say that's the same as the number of authors in the data set.
该参数的值与数据集中的作者数相同
And the second argument is going to be how many folds do I want to look at.
另一个参数是我想查看多少个折
In this case, the answer is two.
在本例中 我选择了两个
This is something that you might want to change though.
你可以更改这些内容
So then what k-fold is going to do is it's going to give me two lists.
KFold 函数的作用就是提供两个列表
The first one is going to be a set of indices of
第一个列表是我要在训练集中使用的
all the data points that I'm going to use in my training set.
所有数据点的索引值的集合
The second list is going to be a list of all of the indices that I'll use in my
第二个列表包含我要在测试数据集中使用的
test data set.
所有索引值
then what I can do is I can use these indices to go into my features and
然后 我可以使用这些索引值进入特征和标签
into my labels and to assign each set of features or each label,
并将各个特征集或标签分配给
to either my training or my testing data set.
训练或测试数据集
So this is the actual partitioning of the data into the training and
这就是将数据划分到训练和测试数据集
testing data sets.
的实际操作
Then, below that it's just like before,
下面的操作与之前类似
we do a little bit of transformation on our training and our testing data.
我们对训练和测试数据进行一些转换
Then we train our classifier and we assess the accuracy.
然后训练分类器 并评估准确性
Now if I just do this out of the box,
如果我直接执行这一操作
something kind of wrong is going to happen.
就有可能会出问题
So let me show you what happens when I run this code.
下面我来演示运行代码时会出现的情况